[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,6,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.44,0:00:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(忆往昔)
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.75,0:00:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  迪恩\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hey, Dean.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.76,0:00:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你回来多久了  -一年了\N{\fnArial\fs30}- How long you been back? - About a year.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.47,0:00:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那你都在做些什么  -猎魔抓鬼\N{\fnArial\fs30}- What have you been doing? - Hunting.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.13,0:00:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一年来你一直都在这世上\N{\fnArial\fs30}You been back practically this whole time?!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.05,0:00:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你终于得偿所愿了  迪恩\N{\fnArial\fs30}You finally had what you wanted, Dean.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.46,0:00:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要的是我弟弟  活着\N{\fnArial\fs30}I wanted my brother, alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.42,0:00:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你渴望的是家庭\N{\fnArial\fs30}You wanted a family.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.60,0:00:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是由于我们的生存方式  你才不得不放弃\N{\fnArial\fs30}You only gave it up because of the way we lived.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.35,0:00:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你已拥有了常人的生活  建立了家庭\N{\fnArial\fs30}But you had something, and you were building something.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.84,0:00:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你去  你就是个猎魔人\N{\fnArial\fs30}I need you to go. You're a hunter.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.00,0:00:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今你弟弟出现了  事情就不一样了\N{\fnArial\fs30}And now you know your brother's out there. Things are different.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.50,0:00:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不想呆这儿了  迪恩  -不  我想\N{\fnArial\fs30}- You don't want to be here, Dean. - Yes, I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.72,0:00:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和本仍会呆在这儿  而\N{\fnArial\fs30}Me and ben will be here, and...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.52,0:00:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要可以你随时都能来\N{\fnArial\fs30}You come when you can.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.75,0:00:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但要答应我完好无损地回来\N{\fnArial\fs30}Just come in one piece.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.17,0:00:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真觉得这样行得通吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}And you really think we could pull something like that off?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.59,0:00:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,值得一试啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}It's worth a shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.88,0:00:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大天使们生性暴戾\N{\fnArial\fs30}Archangels are fierce.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.41,0:00:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且专制跋扈\N{\fnArial\fs30}They're absolute.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.02,0:00:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是天堂最令人生畏的武器\N{\fnArial\fs30}They're heaven's most terrifying weapon.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.20,0:00:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉斐尔\N{\fnArial\fs30}Raphael.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.62,0:00:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来抓我啊  你个小混球\N{\fnArial\fs30}Come and get me, you little bastard.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.98,0:00:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西迪奥\N{\fnArial\fs30}Castiel.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.79,0:00:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当圣油点燃时\N{\fnArial\fs30}When the oil burns,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.09,0:01:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何天使都无法触碰或是跨越那些火焰\N{\fnArial\fs30}no angel can touch or pass through the flames,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.67,0:01:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则他就会死\N{\fnArial\fs30}or he dies.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.07,0:01:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西迪奥\N{\fnArial\fs30}Castiel.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.74,0:01:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要警告你\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm warning you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.96,0:01:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把我留在这儿\N{\fnArial\fs30}Do not leave me here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.43,0:01:09.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则我定找你算账的\N{\fnArial\fs30}I will find you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.66,0:01:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在打算怎么办\N{\fnArial\fs30}What are you gonna do now?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.96,0:01:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想  得回天堂去  -回天堂\N{\fnArial\fs30}- Return to heaven, I suppose. - Heaven?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.15,0:01:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于米迦勒也关进了牢笼\N{\fnArial\fs30}With Michael in the cage,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.44,0:01:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢肯定如今的天堂定群龙无首  乱作一团\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm sure it's total anarchy up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.20,0:01:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(如今)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.54,0:01:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢  不是吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.46,0:02:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么鬼\N{\fnArial\fs30}What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.10,0:02:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  伙计  我们得出发了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Come on, man. Let's get going.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.48,0:02:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老杰\N{\fnArial\fs30}Jerry?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.80,0:02:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃德  我想我正大出血\N{\fnArial\fs30}Ed, I think I'm bleeding.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.71,0:02:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[邪恶力量 第6季第3集]
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.44,0:02:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  帅哥\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hey, you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.36,0:02:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.16,0:04:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别因为我的出现就停下来啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}Don't stop on my account.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.07,0:04:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经完事儿了\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm done.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.41,0:04:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚真是个\N{\fnArial\fs30}Last night was a...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.65,0:04:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高潮迭起之夜  希望你不介意我这样说\N{\fnArial\fs30}High point, if you don't mind me saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.60,0:04:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fnArial\fs30}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.97,0:04:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.75,0:04:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来对你而言新的一天已经开始了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Well, I see you need to start your day.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.92,0:04:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你什么时候出城来着\N{\fnArial\fs30}When did you say you were heading out?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.06,0:04:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没说过  对吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}You didn't. Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.33,0:04:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的  你还真是会玩儿神秘\N{\fnArial\fs30}Damn, you know how to play that mystery card.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.13,0:04:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦对\N{\fnArial\fs30}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.52,0:04:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差点儿都忘了\N{\fnArial\fs30}I almost forgot.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.27,0:04:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次\N{\fnArial\fs30}Next time...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.96,0:04:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以在我下班的时候找我\N{\fnArial\fs30}You can call me on my night off.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.47,0:04:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想的话\N{\fnArial\fs30}If you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.79,0:05:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.30,0:05:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.36,0:05:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-喂  -嘿\N{\fnArial\fs30}- Hey. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.77,0:05:23.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我离坎贝尔大本营还有八小时了\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm about eight hours out of the Campbell base.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.58,0:05:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计划有变\N{\fnArial\fs30}Uh, change of plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.62,0:05:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你来找我  我在宾州的伊斯特尔镇\N{\fnArial\fs30}I need you to meet me. I'm in P.A. -- Town called Easter.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.25,0:05:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在宾夕法尼亚干嘛\N{\fnArial\fs30}What are you doing in Pennsylvania?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.79,0:05:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟一个案子\N{\fnArial\fs30}Caught a case.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.14,0:05:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个案子\N{\fnArial\fs30}A case?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.41,0:05:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候  这不才过了一天半么\N{\fnArial\fs30}When? It's been like a day and a half.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.21,0:05:35.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢找活儿干\N{\fnArial\fs30}I like to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.34,0:05:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显而易见\N{\fnArial\fs30}Apparently.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.22,0:05:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴咱俩又开始纠结互喷了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Glad we hashed that out.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.91,0:05:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到镇时再打给我\N{\fnArial\fs30}Call me when you roll into town.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.52,0:05:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这丫跟谁装老大呢\N{\fnArial\fs30}Who died and made you boss?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.43,0:06:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以再快点儿\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, you could do better than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.31,0:06:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找我啥事儿\N{\fnArial\fs30}Why are you calling me?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.74,0:06:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经死了  不是吗  就这样了\N{\fnArial\fs30}He's dead, right? That's it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.82,0:06:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  我不想再讨论这事儿了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Now, I don't want to talk about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.06,0:06:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好我们该做的\N{\fnArial\fs30}We do what we do --
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.54,0:06:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们按时上班  出席葬礼\N{\fnArial\fs30}We go to work, we go to the funeral.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.32,0:06:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点\N{\fnArial\fs30}Calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.62,0:06:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事和你我都无关\N{\fnArial\fs30}This is nothing to do with you and me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.46,0:06:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你调整好自己情绪  别再打给我了\N{\fnArial\fs30}You're just working yourself up. Don't call me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.23,0:07:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呆瓜\N{\fnArial\fs30}Idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.82,0:07:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}God!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.82,0:07:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}God!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.68,0:07:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调度中心  这是\N{\fnArial\fs30}Dispatch, this is --
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.68,0:07:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劳驾  我  我需要\N{\fnArial\fs30}please, I -- I need...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.24,0:07:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fnArial\fs30}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.38,0:07:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本  我知道你在撒谎\N{\fnArial\fs30}Ben...I know you're lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.37,0:07:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我可是这方面的专家  你骗不了我\N{\fnArial\fs30}Because I lie professionally, that's how.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.04,0:07:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在告诉你妈  是你打破那该死的东西\N{\fnArial\fs30}Now tell your mom that you broke the damn thing
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.39,0:07:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像个男子汉一样负起责任来\N{\fnArial\fs30}and take it like a man.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.65,0:07:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听懂了吗  好的  乖\N{\fnArial\fs30}Okay? Ok-- okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.90,0:07:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛\N{\fnArial\fs30}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.52,0:08:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  竟然在培育祖国未来花朵  真难想象\N{\fnArial\fs30}You -- molding the minds of tomorrow. Who knew?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.72,0:08:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说不是呢\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, tell me about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.36,0:08:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么样了  -什么  \N{\fnArial\fs30}- How'd it go? - With?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.82,0:08:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和莉莎\N{\fnArial\fs30}You and Lisa.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.37,0:08:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于你的离开她有什么反应\N{\fnArial\fs30}How'd she take it when you bailed?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.91,0:08:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  她非常地冷静\N{\fnArial\fs30}Shockingly cool, actually.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.91,0:08:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样对大家都好\N{\fnArial\fs30}Better for everybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.52,0:08:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我想是的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, I suppose.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.59,0:08:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在开这破玩意儿么\N{\fnArial\fs30}Still driving the plastic piece of crap, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.99,0:08:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你的算是废物再利用吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}What's your mileage, again?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.45,0:08:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴\N{\fnArial\fs30}Shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.97,0:08:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,林肯大街740号\N警察局
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.18,0:08:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停尸房
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.66,0:08:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰拉德·哈奇警官  17年的老手\N{\fnArial\fs30}Officer Gerald Hatch -- 17-year veteran,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.25,0:08:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三天前被发现死在警察准备室\N{\fnArial\fs30}found dead in the ready room three days ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.30,0:08:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还真是水分过多了啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}Somebody was over-hydrated.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.87,0:08:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本上  是这样\N{\fnArial\fs30}basically, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.83,0:08:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙差不多是  液化了\N{\fnArial\fs30}The guy just... Liquefied.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.91,0:08:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分的肌肉  骨头  致密的结缔组织\N{\fnArial\fs30}Most of the meat, bones, dense tissues --
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.87,0:08:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都转变成了血\N{\fnArial\fs30}They just turned to blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.90,0:08:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  我真搞不懂  -没人搞得懂\N{\fnArial\fs30}- Okay, I don't get it. - Nobody gets it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.16,0:08:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你说的我懂了\N{\fnArial\fs30}No. I mean, I get that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.96,0:08:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  这个人都成一滩血水了\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm saying, if the guy was a mop job,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.51,0:08:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还来停尸房做什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}then what are we doing in the morgue?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.54,0:08:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还留下什么部件可以看吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}What's left of him to look at?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.86,0:08:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这里不是看他\N{\fnArial\fs30}Not here to look at him.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.70,0:08:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里\N{\fnArial\fs30}Here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.74,0:09:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真恶心\N{\fnArial\fs30}Ooh. Bad news.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.82,0:09:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是托比·格雷警官\N{\fnArial\fs30}Officer Toby Gray.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.07,0:09:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他刚刚被放进来\N{\fnArial\fs30}They just brought him in.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.11,0:09:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被发现死在巡逻车里\N{\fnArial\fs30}Found him dead in his patrol car,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.63,0:09:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时车停在城外的车速监视区\N{\fnArial\fs30}sitting at a speed trap on the outside of town.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.75,0:09:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"严重过敏反应"\N{\fnArial\fs30}"Extreme allergic reaction."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.50,0:09:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  脓疮  从头到脚长满全身\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah. Boils. Covered from head to toe.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.47,0:09:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,体内也有\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, on the inside, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.50,0:09:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面说他的气道里也塞满了\N{\fnArial\fs30}It says his airways are chock full of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.64,0:09:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得是巫术搞的鬼么\N{\fnArial\fs30}This startin' to look a little witchy to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.94,0:09:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始我也这么想\N{\fnArial\fs30}That was my first instinct,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.90,0:09:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我没发现任何巫术的迹象\N{\fnArial\fs30}but I found zero signs of hexwork anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.59,0:09:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就我看来  肯定不是巫术什么的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Far as I can tell, witchcraft was not involved.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.06,0:09:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个一滩血水男和这个脓疮男\N{\fnArial\fs30}There's got to be some sort of link
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.24,0:09:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是有联系的\N{\fnArial\fs30}between, uh, skid mark and bubble wrap here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.84,0:09:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毋庸置疑\N{\fnArial\fs30}No question.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.64,0:09:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有目击证人吗  -有\N{\fnArial\fs30}- All right, well, can I get a witness? - Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.51,0:09:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德·克尔法克斯警官\N{\fnArial\fs30}Officer Ed Colfax.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.22,0:09:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲眼看见哈奇的身体瞬间崩塌成一滩血水\N{\fnArial\fs30}Saw Hatch go from a solid to a liquid.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.86,0:09:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又一个警察\N{\fnArial\fs30}Another cop?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.22,0:09:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈奇的搭档\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hatch's partner.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.68,0:10:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...\N{\fnArial\fs30}Were you, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.19,0:10:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在和我赛车吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Were you racing me?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.30,0:10:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.90,0:10:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想给你点颜色瞧瞧\N{\fnArial\fs30}I was kicking your ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.94,0:10:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是成熟懂事啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}Very mature.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.51,0:10:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克尔法克斯警官在家吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hello? Officer Colfax?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.46,0:10:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神探哥  眼神很犀利嘛\N{\fnArial\fs30}Lookin' sharp, Kojak.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.98,0:10:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是谁\N{\fnArial\fs30}Who the hell are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.34,0:10:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德  我们是联邦调查局的\N{\fnArial\fs30}We're the fed, Ed.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.86,0:10:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的搭档离奇死亡\N{\fnArial\fs30}We're here to ask you a few follow-up questions
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.44,0:10:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想就此问你几个问题\N{\fnArial\fs30}about your partner's death.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.43,0:10:33.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别费心了  这不关你们的事\N{\fnArial\fs30}Don't worry about it. It's nobody's business.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.56,0:10:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-克尔法克斯警官  -少多管闲事\N{\fnArial\fs30}- Officer Colfax  - Don't worry about it!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.69,0:10:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老弟\N{\fnArial\fs30}Dude!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.35,0:10:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克尔法克斯警官\N{\fnArial\fs30}Officer Colfax?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.20,0:11:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  你没事吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hey, man, you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.37,0:11:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别多管闲事\N{\fnArial\fs30}Don't worry about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.50,0:11:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.23,0:11:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  克尔法克斯警官  爱德\N{\fnArial\fs30}Look, officer Colfax -- ed.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.31,0:11:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们认为你的搭档是非正常死亡 \N{\fnArial\fs30}We think that your partner died of unnatural causes.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.65,0:11:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道他有什么仇家吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Did he have any enemies that you know of?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.26,0:11:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以说有\N{\fnArial\fs30}you might say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.58,0:11:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.02,0:11:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁\N{\fnArial\fs30}Who's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.35,0:11:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们俩是咎由自取  我也是\N{\fnArial\fs30}They both had it coming. Me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.45,0:11:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个死的就是我\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'll be the next to go,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.59,0:11:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后这事儿就完了\N{\fnArial\fs30}and then it'll be over.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.25,0:11:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝肯定心满意足了\N{\fnArial\fs30}And god will be satisfied.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.21,0:11:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝干嘛要你们全都去死\N{\fnArial\fs30}Why does god want you all dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.80,0:11:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为克里斯多夫·伯奇\N{\fnArial\fs30}'cause of Christopher Birch.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.36,0:11:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.25,0:11:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是克里斯多夫·伯奇\N{\fnArial\fs30}Who's Christopher Birch?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.58,0:11:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他没有脸\N{\fnArial\fs30}He has no face.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.53,0:11:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德\N{\fnArial\fs30}Ed?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.57,0:11:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警官你没事吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Officer, you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.01,0:12:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德  谁是克里斯多夫·伯奇\N{\fnArial\fs30}Who is Christopher Birch, Ed?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.52,0:12:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德\N{\fnArial\fs30}Ed!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.28,0:12:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克里斯多夫·伯奇是一个没有脸的小孩\N{\fnArial\fs30}Christopher Birch is a kid with no face...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.13,0:12:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有栽赃的枪\N{\fnArial\fs30}...and a planted gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.16,0:12:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你\N{\fnArial\fs30}Uh, you, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.90,0:12:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这有点东西\N{\fnArial\fs30}You got a little something...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.65,0:12:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那里\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.95,0:12:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我靠\N{\fnArial\fs30}Damn.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.34,0:12:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的头就像脏内裤一样痒死了\N{\fnArial\fs30}My head's been itching like a dirty jock.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.93,0:12:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德\N{\fnArial\fs30}Ed?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.32,0:12:41.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.63,0:12:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到了吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}You hear that?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.18,0:13:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷啊  鲜血  脓疮  蝗虫\N{\fnArial\fs30}Sweet. Blood, boils, locusts.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.44,0:13:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃及最盛行的三种瘟疫\N{\fnArial\fs30}Three of your more popular egyptian plagues.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.74,0:13:13.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这些小东西\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, but these guys...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.05,0:13:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从警察的脑袋里钻出来\N{\fnArial\fs30}ate their way out of a cop's melon.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.37,0:13:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金·詹姆士版的圣经上可没这么写\N{\fnArial\fs30}I don't quite remember that in the King James.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.47,0:13:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与此同时  上个月一场警车追逐战中\N{\fnArial\fs30}Meanwhile, a kid named Christopher Birch
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.48,0:13:21.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个叫克里斯多夫·伯奇的小孩\N{\fnArial\fs30}was shot in the head last month
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.88,0:13:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头部中枪而亡\N{\fnArial\fs30}after a vehicle pursuit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.04,0:13:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈奇  格雷和克尔法克斯都有参与此事\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hatch, Gray, and Colfax were the three officers involved,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.43,0:13:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们三人的警方报告一模一样\N{\fnArial\fs30}and they all filed the exact same police report.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.58,0:13:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嫌犯持枪走下了车\N{\fnArial\fs30}"Suspect exited vehicle brandishing a firearm.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.86,0:13:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们被迫开枪"\N{\fnArial\fs30}We were forced to fire."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.08,0:13:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"只有一个没有脸的小孩\N{\fnArial\fs30}"Just a kid with no face 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.72,0:13:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和一把栽赃的枪"\N{\fnArial\fs30}and a planted gun."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.74,0:13:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一群混蛋\N{\fnArial\fs30}Bunch of dicks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.93,0:13:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们杀了这个孩子  还栽赃嫁祸\N{\fnArial\fs30}So they pop the kid, plant the piece.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.28,0:13:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克尔法克斯也许是对的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Maybe Colfax is right.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.50,0:13:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天有眼  这些坏警察恶有恶报\N{\fnArial\fs30}You know, maybe heaven has a hate-on for bad cops.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.42,0:13:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要相信这个脑袋里有虫的警察吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}So we're listening to the guy with the bug in his custard?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.95,0:13:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是\N{\fnArial\fs30}That's -- that's the, uh,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.29,0:13:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的相信这一套啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}The theory you want to go with?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.90,0:13:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪恩  天使们该做点事儿了啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}Dean, angels got to have something to do, right,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.32,0:13:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在是后天启时期\N{\fnArial\fs30}Now that we're post-apocalypse?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.04,0:14:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  可能吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.50,0:14:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们召唤卡西吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}We should call Cass.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.65,0:14:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开玩笑吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}You're kidding, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.02,0:14:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪恩  我试过了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Dean, I tried.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.45,0:14:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一回到上面来\N{\fnArial\fs30}It was the first and second and third thing I did,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.36,0:14:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就整天召唤卡西\N{\fnArial\fs30}soon as I got topside.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.77,0:14:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个龟儿子没反应啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}son of a bitch won't answer the phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.68,0:14:22.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试试吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Well, let's give it a shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.41,0:14:24.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我沉入梦乡\N{\fnArial\fs30}Now I lay me down to sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.90,0:14:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愿卡西迪奥能扇着他毛茸茸的翅膀飞下来\N{\fnArial\fs30}I pray to Castiel to get his feathery ass down here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.34,0:14:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你真白痴啊  -乐观点嘛\N{\fnArial\fs30}- You're an idiot. - Stay positive.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.26,0:14:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很乐观啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, I am positive.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.36,0:14:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西  快快显身\N{\fnArial\fs30}Come on, Cass!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.37,0:14:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别讨打哦\N{\fnArial\fs30}Don't be a dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.67,0:14:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们\N{\fnArial\fs30}We got ourselves a...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.78,0:14:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇到了一个瘟疫啥的状况\N{\fnArial\fs30}Plague-like situation down here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.73,0:14:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你收到了吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Do you...Do you copy?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.91,0:14:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如我所说\N{\fnArial\fs30}Like I said...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.81,0:15:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个小混蛋不会理你的\N{\fnArial\fs30}The son of a bitch doesn't answer --
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.48,0:15:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在就在我身后  是吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}He's right behind me, isn't he?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.68,0:15:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.04,0:15:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.10,0:15:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.51,0:15:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你好"\N{\fnArial\fs30}"Hello."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.15,0:15:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"你好"\N{\fnArial\fs30}"Hello"?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.48,0:15:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃  这句话用来问好没错吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Uh, that is still the term?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.49,0:15:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那么长时间一直在努力联系你\N{\fnArial\fs30}I spent all that time trying to get through to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.97,0:15:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪恩只呼唤了你这么一次\N{\fnArial\fs30}Dean calls once,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.85,0:15:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就出来跟我们说"你好"\N{\fnArial\fs30}and now it's "Hello"?!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.76,0:15:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.44,0:15:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你现在是更爱他还是怎样\N{\fnArial\fs30}So, what, you -- you like him better or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.15,0:15:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪恩和我确实有更深层次的羁绊\N{\fnArial\fs30}Dean and I do share a more profound bond.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.84,0:15:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来不想提的\N{\fnArial\fs30}I wasn't gonna mention it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.92,0:15:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西  我觉得他想说的是\N{\fnArial\fs30}Cass, I think what he's trying to say is that...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.77,0:15:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他曾经为了我们去了地狱\N{\fnArial\fs30}He went to hell for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.52,0:15:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  他为了大家牺牲了自己\N{\fnArial\fs30}I mean, he really took one for the team.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.64,0:15:57.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}You remember that?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.69,0:16:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后他莫名其妙地回来了\N{\fnArial\fs30}And then he comes back without a clue,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.34,0:16:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你却该死的连花五分钟时间\N{\fnArial\fs30}and you can't take five friggin' minutes
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.79,0:16:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他个答案都不肯吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}to give him some answers?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.71,0:16:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我知道答案  我会回应的\N{\fnArial\fs30}If I had any answers, I might have responded.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.57,0:16:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我真的不知道  萨姆\N{\fnArial\fs30}But I don't know, Sam.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.13,0:16:09.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也不知道究竟谁把你从那牢笼解放的\N{\fnArial\fs30}We have no idea who brought you back from the cage...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.60,0:16:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者他为什么解放你\N{\fnArial\fs30}Or why.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.88,0:16:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  不是上帝吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}So...It wasn't god?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.76,0:16:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都没人看见过上帝\N{\fnArial\fs30}No one's even seen god.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.27,0:16:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这整件事都透着诡异\N{\fnArial\fs30}The whole thing remains mysterious.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.68,0:16:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这又是什么意思\N{\fnArial\fs30}What the hell does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.37,0:16:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我也不知道"这句话里\N{\fnArial\fs30}What part of "I don't know"
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.45,0:16:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪个字你不懂\N{\fnArial\fs30}escapes your understanding?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.19,0:16:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西  听着  萨姆呼唤你就该回应\N{\fnArial\fs30}Cass, look, if Sam calls, you answer. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.05,0:16:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你扑闪着小翅膀飞过来\N{\fnArial\fs30}You wing your ass down here,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.31,0:16:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后告诉他"我不知道"\N{\fnArial\fs30}and you tell him, "I don't know."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.36,0:16:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是因为我俩之间有什么羁绊啥的...\N{\fnArial\fs30}Just because we have some sort of a -- a bond or whatever...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.14,0:16:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我来是因为你呼唤了我吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}You think I came because you called?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.14,0:16:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过来是为了这个\N{\fnArial\fs30}I came because of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.49,0:16:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  我们可真想知道这到底怎么回事\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, well, it's nice to know what matters.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.10,0:16:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我大概能猜到是什么干的\N{\fnArial\fs30}It does help one to focus.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.60,0:16:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  你和那个天使巡逻队\N{\fnArial\fs30}Wait, so -- so you and the halo patrol,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.11,0:16:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你们造成的这些杀戮吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}you guys aren't the cause of these killings?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.08,0:16:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\fnArial\fs30}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.78,0:16:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们确实是被我们的某种武器杀死的\N{\fnArial\fs30}But they were committed with one of our weapons.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.36,0:16:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个东西\N{\fnArial\fs30}There's only one thing
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.26,0:16:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够造成这些死状\N{\fnArial\fs30}that could have brought this into existence.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.11,0:17:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们叫它摩西之杖\N{\fnArial\fs30}You call it the staff of Moses.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.50,0:17:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个权杖\N{\fnArial\fs30}The staff?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.66,0:17:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就我所知\N{\fnArial\fs30}It was used
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.62,0:17:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它曾经被用来反抗埃及统治者\N{\fnArial\fs30}in a dominance display against the egyptians, as I recall.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.90,0:17:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  书里都写着呢\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah. That one made the papers.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.06,0:17:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那根权杖不是足以\N{\fnArial\fs30}B-but I thought the staff
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.78,0:17:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让世间血流成河吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}turned, like, a-a river into blood
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.98,0:17:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么就杀这么一个人\N{\fnArial\fs30}not one dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.59,0:17:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还不是这种武器能造成的最大伤害\N{\fnArial\fs30}The weapon isn't being used at full capacity.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.94,0:17:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这不是摩西本人干的\N{\fnArial\fs30}I think we can rule Moses out as a suspect.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.33,0:17:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  但是...\N{\fnArial\fs30}Okay, but...What is --
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.07,0:17:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查克·赫斯顿的那根小棒棒怎么会在人间\N{\fnArial\fs30}What is Chuck Heston's disco stick doing down here, anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.07,0:17:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}Charlton Heston: 美国演员  曾出演过摩西一角
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.20,0:17:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们难道不会把玩具收收好吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}I mean, don't you guys put away your toys?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.90,0:17:36.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在天启之前\N{\fnArial\fs30}Before the apocalypse,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.42,0:17:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天堂虽然已经堕落  但至少依旧稳固\N{\fnArial\fs30}heaven may have been corrupt, but it was stable.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.52,0:17:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,权杖被安稳地保存着\N{\fnArial\fs30}The staff was safely contained.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.68,0:17:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那次战争之后上面就混乱不堪\N{\fnArial\fs30}It's been chaos up there since the war ended.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.03,0:17:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混乱之中  很多很多\N{\fnArial\fs30}In that confusion, a number of...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.22,0:17:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀伤性很强的武器\N{\fnArial\fs30}powerful weapons were...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.46,0:17:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被盗了\N{\fnArial\fs30}stolen.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.58,0:17:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  是说你们那些武器随时都可能发飙\N{\fnArial\fs30}Wait, you -- you're saying your nukes are loose?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.70,0:17:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, I'm afraid so.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.31,0:18:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你们遇上了其中一个\N{\fnArial\fs30}But you've stumbled onto one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.38,0:18:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须找到造成这一切的武器\N{\fnArial\fs30}We must find the weapon that did this.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.28,0:18:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你们的帮助\N{\fnArial\fs30}I need your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.68,0:18:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太给力了  真的\N{\fnArial\fs30}That's rich. Really.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.93,0:18:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨姆  迪恩\N{\fnArial\fs30}Sam, Dean,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.80,0:18:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的"人类技能"已经"生疏"了\N{\fnArial\fs30}My "people skills" are "rusty."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.66,0:18:24.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉  不过我过去一整"年"\N{\fnArial\fs30}Pardon me, but I have spent the last "Year"
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.33,0:18:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都在充当着帮助你们的\N{\fnArial\fs30}as a multi-dimensional wavelength
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.71,0:18:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天堂形象大使的角色\N{\fnArial\fs30}of celestial intent.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.52,0:18:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是相信我\N{\fnArial\fs30}But believe me,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.55,0:18:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们绝对不希望那武器来到世间\N{\fnArial\fs30}you do not want that weapon down here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.57,0:18:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我找到它\N{\fnArial\fs30}Help me find it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.69,0:18:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则将有更多的人死去\N{\fnArial\fs30}Or more people will die.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.83,0:18:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  -好的\N{\fnArial\fs30}- All right. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.23,0:18:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  既然不是天使干的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Well, if the angels didn't pull the trigger,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.14,0:18:42.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们还是从动机查起吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}then that brings us back to motive.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.46,0:18:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.35,0:18:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到案件本身\N{\fnArial\fs30}Back to the case.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.17,0:18:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  已经死了三个警察\N{\fnArial\fs30}Right now, we got three dead cops.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.40,0:18:51.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一能将他们联系到一起的是\N{\fnArial\fs30}Only thing linking them...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.62,0:18:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个\N{\fnArial\fs30}...is this.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.71,0:18:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"已故嫌疑犯的父亲要求彻查此案"\N{\fnArial\fs30}"Father of slain suspect calls for investigation."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.37,0:19:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[星星公报]已故嫌疑犯的父亲要求彻查此案
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.81,0:19:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[东方鹰报]一名警察在执勤中死去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.99,0:19:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  老爸\N{\fnArial\fs30}Come on, dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.72,0:19:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底要读多少遍那个东西\N{\fnArial\fs30}How many times are you gonna read that thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.11,0:19:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  我们应该忘掉那件事情\N{\fnArial\fs30}You know what? We should just throw it away.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.20,0:19:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出去玩吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Go out back and play.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.72,0:19:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西  下次先提个醒好不\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, Cass, a little warning next time.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.83,0:19:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我靠\N{\fnArial\fs30}What the...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.46,0:19:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是怎么进来的\N{\fnArial\fs30}How'd you get in here?!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.41,0:19:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯奇先生  别害怕\N{\fnArial\fs30}Mr. Birch, settle down.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.15,0:19:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是联邦探员\N{\fnArial\fs30}Federal agents.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.02,0:19:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你们不能肆无忌惮地就闯进来吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}But you can't just walk in here!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.42,0:19:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的收藏不少哇\N{\fnArial\fs30}Quite a collection you've got there, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.86,0:19:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说什么...\N{\fnArial\fs30}What are you trying to --
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.85,0:19:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我们知道事情的真相\N{\fnArial\fs30}Look, we know the truth, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.06,0:19:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那些警察对克里斯开枪的时候\N{\fnArial\fs30}Chris didn't have a gun on him 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.27,0:19:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他并没有枪\N{\fnArial\fs30}when those cops shot him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.90,0:19:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们诬陷他\N{\fnArial\fs30}They set him up.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.06,0:19:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.01,0:19:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们总算得到报应了\N{\fnArial\fs30}They're all getting theirs.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.51,0:19:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是谁在对他们进行报复呢  达里尔\N{\fnArial\fs30}And who's giving it to them, Darryl?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.58,0:19:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔\N{\fnArial\fs30}Darryl?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.68,0:19:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你杀了托比·格雷及其他人吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Did you kill Toby Gray and the others? 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.20,0:19:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我没有杀任何人\N{\fnArial\fs30}Me?! I didn't kill anyone! 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.00,0:19:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看看他们的死相\N{\fnArial\fs30}Look at how they died!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.02,0:20:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你用摩西之杖攻击了他们\N{\fnArial\fs30}You smote them with the staff of Moses!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.01,0:20:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你算哪门子的条子啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}The hell kind of fed are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.39,0:20:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没时间了\N{\fnArial\fs30}We don't have time for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.90,0:20:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那东西在哪儿\N{\fnArial\fs30}Where is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.71,0:20:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动我爸\N{\fnArial\fs30}Leave my dad alone!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.50,0:20:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那难不成是...  -没错\N{\fnArial\fs30}- Is that...? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.08,0:20:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不应该是个大家伙吗  -没错\N{\fnArial\fs30}- Shouldn't it be bigger? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.98,0:20:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个...  是被锯掉了\N{\fnArial\fs30}It's -- it's been sawed off.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.89,0:20:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-放了他  不关他的事  -艾伦  快离开这\N{\fnArial\fs30}- Leave him alone! It wasn't him! - Aaron, get out of here!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.59,0:20:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你把他怎么了  -没事  他只是睡着了\N{\fnArial\fs30}- What did you do to him? - It's all right. He's just sleeping.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.03,0:20:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西  温柔点\N{\fnArial\fs30}Cass, take it easy!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.89,0:20:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好  我们不是来伤害你们的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Listen, we're not here to hurt you, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.10,0:20:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只需知道...\N{\fnArial\fs30}But we need to know...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.88,0:20:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从哪里得到这东西的\N{\fnArial\fs30}where did you get this thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.66,0:20:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你们别杀我爸爸\N{\fnArial\fs30}Please don't kill my dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.64,0:20:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我  是我干的\N{\fnArial\fs30}It was me. I did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.35,0:20:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  没人要杀人\N{\fnArial\fs30}Okay, nobody's killing anybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.57,0:20:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}What's your name?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.48,0:20:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾伦·伯奇\N{\fnArial\fs30}Aaron. Aaron Birch.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.61,0:20:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的艾伦·伯奇  你从哪得到的这个\N{\fnArial\fs30}Okay, Aaron Birch, where did you get this?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.92,0:20:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你肯定不信  -说说看\N{\fnArial\fs30}- You won't believe me. - Try me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.92,0:20:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一个天使给我的\N{\fnArial\fs30}It was an angel.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.08,0:21:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天使\N{\fnArial\fs30}An angel?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.64,0:21:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些骗子  他们杀了我哥哥\N{\fnArial\fs30}Those liars, they killed my brother,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.85,0:21:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却没有任何报应\N{\fnArial\fs30}and nothing bad even happened to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.21,0:21:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不公平\N{\fnArial\fs30}It's not fair.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.68,0:21:11.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我每晚祈求上帝  给他们应有的惩罚\N{\fnArial\fs30}So I prayed to god every night he would punish them.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.65,0:21:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而上帝却从未回应\N{\fnArial\fs30}God didn't answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.74,0:21:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他回应了\N{\fnArial\fs30}But he did.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.19,0:21:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫什么  有没有告诉过你\N{\fnArial\fs30}His name -- did he give you a name?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.59,0:21:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fnArial\fs30}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.73,0:21:21.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说我可以获得正义\N{\fnArial\fs30}He just said I could have justice,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.12,0:21:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我要自己去争取\N{\fnArial\fs30}but I was gonna have to take it myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.17,0:21:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他...  他给了我这根木棒\N{\fnArial\fs30}He...He gave me the stick.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.31,0:21:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就...  这么给你了\N{\fnArial\fs30}He just... Gave it to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.84,0:21:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Ah, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.04,0:21:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不可能就这么白给你吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}He didn't just give it to you,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.03,0:21:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧  艾伦\N{\fnArial\fs30}did he, Aaron?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.14,0:21:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我买来的\N{\fnArial\fs30}I bought it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.74,0:21:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买来的\N{\fnArial\fs30}You bought it?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.01,0:21:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用什么买\N{\fnArial\fs30}With what?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.63,0:21:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有啥好给他的\N{\fnArial\fs30}What's your allowance?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.54,0:21:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个天使想要什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}What did the angel want for it?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.19,0:21:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给了他什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}What did you give him for it?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.18,0:21:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的灵魂\N{\fnArial\fs30}My soul.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.54,0:22:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把灵魂卖给了一个天使\N{\fnArial\fs30}You sold your soul to an angel?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.15,0:22:07.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可能吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Can that even happen?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.68,0:22:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前从没发生过\N{\fnArial\fs30}It's never happened before.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.16,0:22:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天使会买灵魂\N{\fnArial\fs30}An angel's buying souls.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.70,0:22:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这倒是解释了他为什么要把这东西锯开\N{\fnArial\fs30}That could explain why he cut the staff into pieces.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.82,0:22:15.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.82,0:22:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器越多  "产品"就越多\N{\fnArial\fs30}More pieces, more product.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.28,0:22:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥叫"产品"  这人到底是谁\N{\fnArial\fs30}More "Product"? Who is this guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.47,0:22:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会找到他的\N{\fnArial\fs30}We'll find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.28,0:22:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你这是干什么  -方便\N{\fnArial\fs30}- What did you do that for? - Portability.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.32,0:22:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西  你知道你这是在拐个孩子吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Cass, you realize you just kidnapped a kid?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.49,0:22:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若我们追踪的那个天使真买了他的灵魂\N{\fnArial\fs30}If the angel we seek truly bought this boy's soul,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.06,0:22:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当一个天使宣布了他对灵魂的所有权\N{\fnArial\fs30}when a claim is laid on a living soul,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.22,0:22:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会留下记号  一个标志\N{\fnArial\fs30}it leaves a mark, a brand.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.77,0:22:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥  就跟校服上的校徽似的么\N{\fnArial\fs30}What, like a -- like a shirt tag at camp?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.57,0:22:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道你说啥\N{\fnArial\fs30}I have no idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.25,0:22:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我能看懂那个记号\N{\fnArial\fs30}But I can read the mark
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.64,0:22:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找出买了这个灵魂的天使叫什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}and find the name of the angel that bought the soul.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.42,0:22:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么看\N{\fnArial\fs30}How?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.07,0:22:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  他要受苦了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Well, painfully for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.00,0:22:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这过程会极其痛苦\N{\fnArial\fs30}The reading will be excruciating.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.63,0:22:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂喂  等等\N{\fnArial\fs30}Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.32,0:22:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-迪恩  -他只是个孩子  卡西\N{\fnArial\fs30}- Dean.- He's a kid, Cass.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.32,0:23:01.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子啊  萨姆你说\N{\fnArial\fs30}A ki-- Sam?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.22,0:23:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会造成永久伤害吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Any permanent damage?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.40,0:23:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说啥  -身体上的伤害极其微小\N{\fnArial\fs30}- What?! - Physically, minimal.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.23,0:23:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得  那您就请随意吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, well, yeah, then by all means,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.76,0:23:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-把胳膊插进去吧  -迪恩\N{\fnArial\fs30}- stick your arm right in there. - Dean!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.89,0:23:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了名字  我就能用一个仪式查到他在哪\N{\fnArial\fs30}If I get the name, I can work a ritual to track the angel down.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.34,0:23:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我双手赞成  但是拜托\N{\fnArial\fs30}And I'm all for that. But come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.72,0:23:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-肯定会有别的办法吧  -没别的办法\N{\fnArial\fs30}- There's got to be another way. - There is no other way.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.42,0:23:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要折磨一个孩子\N{\fnArial\fs30}You're gonna torture a kid?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.88,0:23:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没闲心管那个了  迪恩\N{\fnArial\fs30}I can't care about that, Dean!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.85,0:23:27.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,良知对我来说是奢侈品\N{\fnArial\fs30}I don't have the luxury.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.48,0:24:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在可以休息了\N{\fnArial\fs30}He'll rest now.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.14,0:24:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道名字了吗  是什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}Did you get a name? What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.78,0:24:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为他在混战中死了\N{\fnArial\fs30}I thought he died in the war.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.19,0:24:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥  他  他是敌是友\N{\fnArial\fs30}What, he -- he was a -- he was a friend or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.30,0:24:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一位挚友\N{\fnArial\fs30}A good friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.72,0:24:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  你的好兄弟现在\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, well, your frat buddy is now 
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.93,0:24:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做起了买卖灵魂的兼职啊  跟恶魔有一拼\N{\fnArial\fs30}moonlighting as a crossroads demon.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.19,0:24:25.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想应该是巴尔萨泽\N{\fnArial\fs30}Balthazar. I wonder...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.46,0:24:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说我们能找到他  对吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}So we can find him now, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.70,0:24:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴尔萨泽\N{\fnArial\fs30}Balthazar.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.12,0:24:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了  卡西迪奥  这名字可真是管了大用了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Thanks, Castiel. We'll make good use of the name.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.84,0:24:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便说一句  拉斐尔向你问好\N{\fnArial\fs30}And by the way, Raphael says hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.31,0:25:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥的车\N{\fnArial\fs30}My car.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.57,0:25:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错  不幸中的万幸\N{\fnArial\fs30}Okay. Silver lining.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.29,0:25:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他跑了\N{\fnArial\fs30}He's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.07,0:25:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西  那是谁\N{\fnArial\fs30}Cass, who was that guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.50,0:25:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉斐尔的手下\N{\fnArial\fs30}A soldier of Raphael.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.39,0:25:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定在我来找你们的时候就跟上我了\N{\fnArial\fs30}He must have followed me when I answered your call.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.00,0:25:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉斐尔  那大天使吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Raphael? The archangel?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.17,0:25:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  这什么情况\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm sorry, what's going on here?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.07,0:26:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我待会再解释  现在我们得...\N{\fnArial\fs30}I can explain later. Right now we have to --
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.24,0:26:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别想待会  停下来  好吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}No, not later. Now. Stop, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.87,0:26:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各种天使来捣乱  卡西\N{\fnArial\fs30}Too many angels, Cass!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.18,0:26:06.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道"谁"先来  "谁"还来\N{\fnArial\fs30}I don't know who's on first, what's on second.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.07,0:26:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁"又来"了\N{\fnArial\fs30}What is "Second"?!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.07,0:26:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}关于这句话有一段经典的视频
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.36,0:26:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跟我咬文嚼字\N{\fnArial\fs30}Don't start that.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.96,0:26:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很简单  拉斐尔和他的追随者们\N{\fnArial\fs30}It is simple -- Raphael and his followers,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.42,0:26:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们想让他去统治天堂\N{\fnArial\fs30}They want him to rule heaven.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.92,0:26:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  还有很多别的天使们\N{\fnArial\fs30}I -- and many others --
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.47,0:26:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们最不想看到的  就是他掌权\N{\fnArial\fs30}The last thing we want is to let him take over.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.91,0:26:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则就是生灵涂炭\N{\fnArial\fs30}It would be catastrophic.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.55,0:26:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在说内战吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}You're talking civil war.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.32,0:26:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多  就是\N{\fnArial\fs30}Technically, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.06,0:26:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们必须在拉斐尔之前找到\N{\fnArial\fs30}Which is why we have to find Balthazar and his weapons
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.27,0:26:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴尔萨泽和他的武器\N{\fnArial\fs30}Before Raphael does.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.34,0:26:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁找到武器  谁就赢定了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Whoever has the weapons wins the war.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.79,0:26:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别客气  尽管用\N{\fnArial\fs30}Help yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.68,0:26:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果拉斐尔赢了会怎样\N{\fnArial\fs30}And what happens if Raphael wins?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.13,0:26:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他想要怎样  -他一直想做的  \N{\fnArial\fs30}- What -- what does he want? - What he's always wanted --
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.07,0:26:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像圣经里写的那样  结束这一切\N{\fnArial\fs30}to end the story the way it was written.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.08,0:26:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说我们阻止的那个天启吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}You mean the apocalypse, the one that we derailed?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.06,0:26:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  就是那个\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yes. That one.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.83,0:26:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉斐尔想要再次开启天启\N{\fnArial\fs30}Raphael wants to put it back on the rails.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.12,0:26:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.85,0:26:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要没药\N{\fnArial\fs30}I need myrrh.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.46,0:26:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没药\N{\fnArial\fs30}Myrrh?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.12,0:26:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦人的小翅膀\N{\fnArial\fs30}Friggin' angels.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.99,0:27:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉斐尔为啥想再弄个天启出来\N{\fnArial\fs30}Why does Raphael want to bring back all this crap?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.27,0:27:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个传统主义者\N{\fnArial\fs30}He's a traditionalist.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.12,0:27:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西  你为何没告诉过我们这些\N{\fnArial\fs30}Cass, why didn't you tell us this?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.68,0:27:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我羞于启齿\N{\fnArial\fs30}I was ashamed.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.05,0:27:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的兄弟们让我很失望\N{\fnArial\fs30}I expected more from my brothers.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.67,0:27:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.93,0:27:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  我需要你的血\N{\fnArial\fs30}Now I need your blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.44,0:27:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不用你自己的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Whoa, whoa! Hey! Ahh! Why don't you use your own?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.33,0:27:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管用  我不是人类\N{\fnArial\fs30}It wouldn't work. I'm not human.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.45,0:27:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[咒语]\N{\fnArial\fs30}Zamran ils soba vpaah zixlai grosb.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.11,0:27:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西\N{\fnArial\fs30}Uh, Cass,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.63,0:27:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这咒语需要多长时间\N{\fnArial\fs30}how long does this spell take?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.10,0:28:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到他了  行动\N{\fnArial\fs30}Got him. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.53,0:28:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么办\N{\fnArial\fs30}Whoa, whoa, whoa. What about him?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.97,0:28:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察会把他送回家的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Don't you think the police will take him home?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.74,0:28:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真没想到还挺有情调\N{\fnArial\fs30}I was expecting more Dr. No, less Liberace.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.74,0:28:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}Dr. No: 诺博士  007系列\N Liberace: 美国钢琴家
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.42,0:29:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西\N{\fnArial\fs30}Cass.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.10,0:29:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来了\N{\fnArial\fs30}You're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.43,0:29:27.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴尔萨泽\N{\fnArial\fs30}Balthazar.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.76,0:29:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真高兴见到你\N{\fnArial\fs30}It's so good to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.47,0:29:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他告诉我你最近到处飞来飞去\N{\fnArial\fs30}He told me you were floating around.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.42,0:29:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他\N{\fnArial\fs30}He?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.09,0:29:35.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩不是一起的么\N{\fnArial\fs30}I believe you two float together.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.98,0:29:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的  声音嘶哑什么的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, you know, the old frog in the throat.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.13,0:29:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连我都知道这笑话太冷了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Even I know that that's a bad joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.68,0:29:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还为你的死表示哀悼来着呢\N{\fnArial\fs30}I grieved your death.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.85,0:29:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦对  关于那个真是不好意思\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, yeah. I'm sorry about that, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.16,0:29:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让他们以为我死了\N{\fnArial\fs30}I wanted them to think, you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.72,0:29:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样  他们就不会来找我了\N{\fnArial\fs30}so... they wouldn't come looking for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.00,0:30:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切是怎么回事\N{\fnArial\fs30}What... is all this?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.45,0:30:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你在干什么  -想干什么就干什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}- What are you doing? - Whatever I want.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.30,0:30:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今早我来了个多人行...\NThis morning I had a ménage à --
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.52,0:30:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法语里12怎么说来着\N{\fnArial\fs30}What's French for 12?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.03,0:30:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你偷了摩西之杖\N{\fnArial\fs30}You stole the staff of Moses.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.09,0:30:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然\N{\fnArial\fs30}Sure, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.57,0:30:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我偷了很多东西\N{\fnArial\fs30}I stole a lot of things.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.13,0:30:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你曾是名值得尊敬的伟大战士\N{\fnArial\fs30}You were a great and honorable soldier.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.28,0:30:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起战斗\N{\fnArial\fs30}We fought together.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.15,0:30:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  已经数不清多少次了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yes, too many times to count.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.70,0:30:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我了解你\N{\fnArial\fs30}I know you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.52,0:30:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是一般的小偷\N{\fnArial\fs30}You're not some common thief.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.33,0:30:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般吗  不\N{\fnArial\fs30}Common? No.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.95,0:30:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小偷吗  嗯\N{\fnArial\fs30}Thief? Eh.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.96,0:30:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你的帮助\N{\fnArial\fs30}I need your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.13,0:30:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fnArial\fs30}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.38,0:30:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的那些事我都听说了\N{\fnArial\fs30}I've been hearing all about you,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.47,0:30:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西  对我来说  你和我...\N{\fnArial\fs30}and as far as I'm concerned, you and me, Cass...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.56,0:30:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切如常\N{\fnArial\fs30}Nothing's changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.18,0:30:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还是兄弟  我当然想帮助你\N{\fnArial\fs30}We're brothers. Of course I want to help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.56,0:30:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fnArial\fs30}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.36,0:30:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要那些武器\N{\fnArial\fs30}I need the weapons.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.66,0:30:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别要这个\N{\fnArial\fs30}Don't ask that.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.08,0:30:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要拿走它们  为何要逃跑\N{\fnArial\fs30}Why take them? Why run away?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.64,0:30:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我做的到\N{\fnArial\fs30}Because I could!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.46,0:30:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fnArial\fs30}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.62,0:30:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  这一切都拜你所赐呢\N{\fnArial\fs30}What? I me-- you're the one who made it possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.53,0:30:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是追随着你的脚步\N{\fnArial\fs30}The footsteps I'm following -- they're yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.03,0:30:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做的那一切  阻止天启\N{\fnArial\fs30}What you did, stopping the big plan,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.23,0:30:59.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背水一战\N{\fnArial\fs30}the prize fight?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.72,0:31:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所做的远不止是背叛天堂\N{\fnArial\fs30}You did more than rebel.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.52,0:31:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你撕毁了整个蓝图\N{\fnArial\fs30}You tore up the whole script 
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.77,0:31:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改变了我们所有人的命运\N{\fnArial\fs30}and burned the pages for all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.39,0:31:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一个新时代\N{\fnArial\fs30}It's a new era.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.52,0:31:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么规则和命运可言\N{\fnArial\fs30}No rules, no destiny.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.68,0:31:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有完完全全的自由\N{\fnArial\fs30}Just utter and complete freedom.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.44,0:31:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你就这样享受这份自由吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}And this is what you do with it? 
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.77,0:31:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管它的呢\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hey, screw it, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.16,0:31:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  爸爸不会回来了\N{\fnArial\fs30}I mean, dad's not coming back.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.90,0:31:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也大可以随心所欲  花天酒地啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}You might as well blow coke and jump on the bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.30,0:31:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你向我证明了  一切皆有可能\N{\fnArial\fs30}You proved to me we could do anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.63,0:31:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我要体验一切可能\N{\fnArial\fs30}so I'm trying everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.51,0:31:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这有什么区别呢\N{\fnArial\fs30}What difference does it make?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.58,0:31:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然有  天上正内战呢\N{\fnArial\fs30}Of course it makes a diff-- it's Civil War up there! 
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.74,0:31:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fnArial\fs30}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.34,0:31:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若能打败拉斐尔\N{\fnArial\fs30}If we can beat raphael, 
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.25,0:31:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就能结束这一切\N{\fnArial\fs30}we can end this!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.64,0:31:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把武器给我\N{\fnArial\fs30}Just give me the weapons.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.44,0:31:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你很可爱的一点是什么吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Do you know what's funny about you?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.13,0:31:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真以为自己能阻止这场战争\N{\fnArial\fs30}You actually believe that you can stop the fighting.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.07,0:31:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它永远不会停止\N{\fnArial\fs30}It will never stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.52,0:31:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我建议  带上些有价值的东西\N{\fnArial\fs30}My advice-- grab something valuable
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.91,0:31:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后佯装自己死了\N{\fnArial\fs30}and fake your own death.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.02,0:32:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经疯了\N{\fnArial\fs30}You've gone insane.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.08,0:32:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你悠哉的日子已经结束了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Your little holiday is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.17,0:32:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在拉斐尔知道你还活着\N{\fnArial\fs30}Raphael knows you're alive by now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.99,0:32:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉斐尔可以随时来找我\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, Raphael can try me anytime.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.80,0:32:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已全副武装\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm armed.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.54,0:32:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  卡西\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm sorry, Cass.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.47,0:32:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抛开其他不谈  见到你我真的很开心\N{\fnArial\fs30}All else aside, I'm really, really happy to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.74,0:32:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你身后有个讨厌的跟屁虫\N{\fnArial\fs30}Even though you still have that stick up your ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.75,0:32:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你干的吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Was that you?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.01,0:32:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是给我的暗号了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, that's my cue then.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.95,0:32:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让拉斐尔去使吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Tell, uh, Raphael to bite me.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.03,0:32:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点  他们狡猾的很\N{\fnArial\fs30}Watch them. They're all snakes.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.47,0:32:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看这边\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hey, there.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.94,0:32:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有一把\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, I got one of those, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.30,0:33:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得自己可以用刀跟天使搏斗吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}You think you can knife fight an angel?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.89,0:33:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁要打架了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Who's fighting?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.49,0:33:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快滚吧  一群孬货\N{\fnArial\fs30}Peace out, douchewad.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.08,0:33:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么做是错的\N{\fnArial\fs30}You're making a mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.73,0:33:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  还有别的解决办法\N{\fnArial\fs30}Please. There is another way.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.33,0:33:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟  拜托  我不想伤害你\N{\fnArial\fs30}Brother, please. I don't want to hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.71,0:33:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们为什么就是不听话呢\N{\fnArial\fs30}Why won't any of you listen?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.38,0:33:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们当然不听  卡西迪奥\N{\fnArial\fs30}They don't listen, Castiel,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.52,0:33:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们的心都是我的\N{\fnArial\fs30}because their hearts are mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.69,0:34:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知何故  我觉得这次上帝不会救你了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Somehow, I don't think god will be bringing you back this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.30,0:34:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我手上这玩意儿\N{\fnArial\fs30}Look at my junk.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.51,0:34:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要\N{\fnArial\fs30}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.17,0:34:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗德的妻子也是这么死的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Same thing happened to Lot's Wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.17,0:34:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}罗德的妻子: 来源于创世纪
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.70,0:34:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碘化这个可怜虫\N{\fnArial\fs30}Iodize the poor sucker, 
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.52,0:34:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一辈子都不用愁没盐用了\N{\fnArial\fs30}and your kitchen is stocked for life.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.22,0:34:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回来了\N{\fnArial\fs30}You came back.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.57,0:34:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在拉斐尔得去买个新皮囊了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Well, now Raphael will have to go shopping for a new vessel.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.34,0:35:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样到他下次换上皮囊前\N{\fnArial\fs30}Should give me a nice long head start on him.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.00,0:35:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都有一段美好的时光\N{\fnArial\fs30}Until next time.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.06,0:35:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一次\N{\fnArial\fs30}Next time.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.66,0:35:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机不可失  失不再来\N{\fnArial\fs30}No time like the present.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.48,0:35:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣火\N{\fnArial\fs30}Holy fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.02,0:35:15.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个无毛的猿类  放了我\N{\fnArial\fs30}You hairless ape! Release me!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.86,0:35:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先去除艾伦·伯奇灵魂上的标记\N{\fnArial\fs30}First you're taking your marker off of Aaron Birch's soul!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.66,0:35:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为何这么做\N{\fnArial\fs30}Am I?!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.55,0:35:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨姆\N{\fnArial\fs30}Sam?!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.56,0:35:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你想尝尝自己的劲脆天使翼\N{\fnArial\fs30}Unless you like your wings extra crispy,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.72,0:35:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会考虑下\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'd think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.00,0:35:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西迪奥  我在天堂帮过你\N{\fnArial\fs30}Castiel, I stood for you in heaven.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.58,0:35:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要让  -我相信\N{\fnArial\fs30}- Are you gonna let...  - I believe...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.74,0:35:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事无毛猿类有发言权\N{\fnArial\fs30}The hairless ape has the floor.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.76,0:35:40.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fnArial\fs30}Very well.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.65,0:35:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那男孩欠我的一笔勾销了  \N{\fnArial\fs30}The boy's debt is cleared. 
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.48,0:35:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的灵魂归他自己所有\N{\fnArial\fs30}His soul is his own.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.20,0:35:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底为什么要买人类的灵魂\N{\fnArial\fs30}Why you buying up human souls, anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.79,0:35:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在当下的经济状况下\N{\fnArial\fs30}In this economy,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.02,0:36:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也许是唯一值得买的东西了\N{\fnArial\fs30}it's probably the only thing worth buying.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.76,0:36:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道灵魂有多大价值么\N{\fnArial\fs30}Do you have any idea what souls are worth?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.85,0:36:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有多大的力量\N{\fnArial\fs30}What power they hold?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.61,0:36:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  放了我\N{\fnArial\fs30}Now...release me.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.12,0:36:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你的  混蛋  没人说过要放你\N{\fnArial\fs30}Suck it, ass clown. Nobody said anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.43,0:36:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西  你搞什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}Cass, what the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.12,0:36:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我欠你的还清了\N{\fnArial\fs30}My debt to you is cleared.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.46,0:36:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fnArial\fs30}Fair enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.07,0:36:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西  你疯了吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Cass, are you out of your mind?!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.51,0:36:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡西\N{\fnArial\fs30}Cass?!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.47,0:36:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的天使们  回来啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, friggin' angels! Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.60,0:36:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.57,0:36:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我在这里放了这么多东西\N{\fnArial\fs30}I didn't realize I had this much stuff back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.33,0:36:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要一些放东西的空间\N{\fnArial\fs30}Well, I need some space.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.23,0:36:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段时间搞到了很多东西\N{\fnArial\fs30}Kind of picked up some stuff along the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.73,0:36:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}What the hell is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.58,0:37:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是本的万圣节面具\N{\fnArial\fs30}Oh, it's, uh, Ben's halloween costume.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.00,0:37:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪怪温迪戈\N{\fnArial\fs30}Wendigo?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.49,0:37:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.09,0:37:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很像啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}Accurate.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.55,0:37:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么\N{\fnArial\fs30}Hey, so, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.19,0:37:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}...are you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.07,0:37:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Me?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.50,0:37:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我很好啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, I'm great.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.56,0:37:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  因为有几次\N{\fnArial\fs30}Really? 'cause there's
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.97,0:37:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我觉得有点奇怪\N{\fnArial\fs30}been a few times that you got me wondering.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.83,0:37:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思\N{\fnArial\fs30}Come again?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.61,0:37:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,例如卡西"虐待"那个孩子的时候\N{\fnArial\fs30}Well, like where were you when Cass was, uh,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.28,0:37:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪了\N{\fnArial\fs30}giving the holy taser treatment to that kid?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.57,0:37:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就在那里啊\N{\fnArial\fs30}I was right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.81,0:37:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.23,0:37:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为老实说\N{\fnArial\fs30}'cause honestly,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.86,0:37:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉只有我站出来反对卡西那么做\N{\fnArial\fs30}I felt like I was the only one raising a card.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.33,0:37:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fnArial\fs30}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.13,0:37:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  我同意你的观点\N{\fnArial\fs30}Uh, I mean, I was with you,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:44.14,0:37:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...\N{\fnArial\fs30}but...I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.67,0:37:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要通过他找到线索\N{\fnArial\fs30}W-we needed the intel.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.91,0:37:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  但那线索是折磨那个孩子得来的\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, I know, but we tortured that kid to get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.64,0:37:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是觉得你\N{\fnArial\fs30}I just didn't get the feeling that you...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.52,0:37:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一点都不关心\N{\fnArial\fs30}that you even cared.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.72,0:38:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你错了\N{\fnArial\fs30}You're wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.22,0:38:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟  我想弄明白这件事是因为\N{\fnArial\fs30}Man, I'm just trying to figure this out because...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.43,0:38:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你变了\N{\fnArial\fs30}something's different with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.00,0:38:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己应该清楚\N{\fnArial\fs30}You know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.89,0:38:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  我知道\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah. Yeah, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.27,0:38:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.67,0:38:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.55,0:38:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说\N{\fnArial\fs30}I mean...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.41,0:38:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去几年我一直在不停地猎魔\N{\fnArial\fs30}I've been hunting nonstop for the past year,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.37,0:38:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,类似...\N{\fnArial\fs30}Kind of...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.26,0:38:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四处奔波  你知道吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Kind of out in the wild, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.08,0:38:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  没错  我是有那么点不拘小节\N{\fnArial\fs30}So, yeah, I suppose I'm a little rough around the edges.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.88,0:38:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  我明白\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah, I get that.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.57,0:38:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是觉得原因应该不止这么简单\N{\fnArial\fs30}I just don't think I'm getting the whole scoop.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.22,0:38:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨姆  你去过地狱\N{\fnArial\fs30}You went to hell, Sam.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.33,0:38:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  我知道那会对人造成怎样的伤害\N{\fnArial\fs30}And believe me, I know what that does to a guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.41,0:38:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你\N{\fnArial\fs30}To you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.59,0:38:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.65,0:38:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那会对你造成怎样的伤害\N{\fnArial\fs30}You know what it does to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.42,0:38:50.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它折磨过你\N{\fnArial\fs30}It -- it tortured you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.12,0:38:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道\N{\fnArial\fs30}You know?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.42,0:38:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得它现在还在影响你\N{\fnArial\fs30}I think it still does.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.45,0:38:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但  迪恩\N{\fnArial\fs30}But, Dean...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.07,0:38:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.91,0:39:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你是说\N{\fnArial\fs30}So you're saying, what,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.75,0:39:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比我坚强\N{\fnArial\fs30}That -- that you're stronger than me?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.19,0:39:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\fnArial\fs30}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.41,0:39:06.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是说我们有所不同\N{\fnArial\fs30}Just saying we're different.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.69,0:39:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近的妖怪们\N{\fnArial\fs30}Monsters lately.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.78,0:39:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的幻觉还是事有蹊跷\N{\fnArial\fs30}Is it me or is it weird?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.21,0:39:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心\N{\fnArial\fs30}Look out!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.39,0:39:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸血鬼吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Vampires?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.18,0:39:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些不是吸血鬼  兄弟\N{\fnArial\fs30}These aren't vampires, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.80,0:39:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是\N{\fnArial\fs30}These...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.96,0:39:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是一群傻逼\N{\fnArial\fs30}These are douche bags.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.92,0:40:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我解释一下到底发生了什么\N{\fnArial\fs30}Explain to me what's going on out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.98,0:40:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莎  我不能把这些烂七八糟的事情带给你\N{\fnArial\fs30}Lis, I can't bring this crap home to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.79,0:40:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说你的工作吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}You're talking about your work.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.74,0:40:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说我的人生\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm talking about my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.87,0:40:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城里的任何人大肆询问真相时\N{\fnArial\fs30}Anyone in town who asks aloud for the truth
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.43,0:40:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会引来真理女神\N{\fnArial\fs30}Invokes Veritas.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.76,0:40:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是简简单单地给你真相\N{\fnArial\fs30}And she doesn't just give it to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.00,0:40:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是用真相猛击你\N{\fnArial\fs30}She slams you with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.27,0:40:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭什么我要告诉你这个\N{\fnArial\fs30}Whoa, why the hell am I telling you this? 
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.88,0:40:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我受了诅咒\N{\fnArial\fs30}Because I'm cursed.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.08,0:40:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说我寻问了真相  猜猜怎么了\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm saying I asked for the truth, and, uh, guess what?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.87,0:40:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了\N{\fnArial\fs30}I'm getting it.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.70,0:40:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就像我之前所说  对你我满肚子疑惑\N{\fnArial\fs30}So, like I said, I have a few questions for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.80,0:40:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪恩  你还好吗\N{\fnArial\fs30}Dean, you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.35,0:40:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲍比  是萨姆的问题\N{\fnArial\fs30}It's Sam, Bobby.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.52,0:40:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有你帮我\N{\fnArial\fs30}You got my back.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.76,0:40:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管发生什么  我都可以信赖你\N{\fnArial\fs30}No matter what happens, I can always count on you,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.91,0:40:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吗  小萨姆\N{\fnArial\fs30}Right, Sammy?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.74,0:40:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了  迪恩\N{\fnArial\fs30}Yeah.Of course,Dean.
